Manoj Bhatt

MBA -Marketing & International Business

Contact Information

Mobile: 91 8904950782

E-mail: manoj0985@qmail.com

Profile

MBA from **Symbiosis Institute of Management Studies, Pune** with more than 2 years of work experience in Corporate Sales and 2 years in Channel Management.

Ability of delivering value-added customer service and achieving customer delight by meeting and exceeding both internal and external customer expectations.

Open to learning and acquiring new professional skills and attributes.

Competencies

Behavioural Interpersonal skills , Presentation skills, Team player,

Problem solving skills, Trustworthy and Accountable.

Professional Ownership at work, Never say die attitude and Out of the box thinking.

Professional Experience

MFI Document Solutions Ltd , Dar Es Salaam (Tanzania)

Position Held: Assistant Manager

• Tenure: Feb 2014 - March 2015

Job Responsibilities:

- ➤ Handle Corporate accounts and upcoming projects.
- > Relationship management- Decision maker and Key corporate personal.
- Manage tenders and local business.
- Manage tenders of Government Entities and design quotations as per need.
- > Help the customers identify suitable product as per need and prepare proposals.
- > Manage RFQs and RFPs.

Idea Cellular Ltd, Bangalore

- Position Held: Assistant Manager, Postpaid Connection
- Tenure: Sep 2013- January 2014

Job Responsibilities:

- > Handled postpaid connection sales portfolio- Corporate client acquisition & retention.
- > Responsible for training & mentoring front line team memmebrs.
- Oranizing and executing BTL activities in catchment spots.

HCL Infosystems Ltd, Indore

- Position Held: Territory Manager
- Tenure: July 2011- June 2013

Job Responsibilities:

- > Responsible for achieving sales target for the defined territory with the help of sales team.
- Managing, guiding and training Channel Sales Team.
- Vendor management.
- New product and sales training for Nokia promoters at key retail outlets.
- Product Incharge for Nokia Accessories, HCL Gaming consoles and Sandisk in assigned territory.

The Pride Hotels, Bangalore

- Position Held: Sales Executive, Regional Sales
- Tenure: June 2007 May 2009

Job Responsibilities:

- Maintaining PR with existing corporate clients and expanding Client base.
- Rate contracting with clients in order to ensure continuous business.
- Keeping track of companies sending corporates to outstations.

Educational Background		
2009 - 2011	Masters of Business Administration - "Marketing" Symbiosis Institute of Management Studies, Pune	2.39/ 4
2003 - 2007	Bachelor of Hotel Management Army Institute of Hotel Management , Bangalore	64 %
2002 to 2003	XII (AISSCE)- "Commerce" Army School, Roorkee Cantt	60.60 %
2000 to 2001	X (AISSE) Army School, Roorkee Cantt	66.00 %

Professional Achievements & Extra-Curricular Activities

- > Awarded for achieving assigned targets at The Pride Hotels between 2008-2009.
- Organized College food festival "Melange" and handled Marketing campaign for the same in 2007.
- > Member of National Service Scheme from the year 2003-2007 and successfully attended two service camps under the campaign "Youth for Cleanliness" & "Water Conservation".
- ➤ Member of Scouts & Guides and attended camps under the campaign "National Integration" in J&K- 1999.

Personal Information

Present Address: H.No.213, Vijayashree Golden Orchid, Devarbessanahalli, Bangalore- 560103

Date of Birth: 25 / March /1985

Hobbies: Outdoor Games, Travelling, Trekking and Swimming

Mobility: Anywhere in India

Reference: On Request